{
    "results": [
        {
            "category": "TTP",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Which cohort number is our group?",
            "correct_answer": "3",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "The very first",
                "6",
                "2"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "TTP",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Who is the nice guy that shared his notes in the slack chat?",
            "correct_answer": "Rafid",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Tenzin",
                "Mohammed",
                "Justin Bieber"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "TTP",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "How many actual days were we in attendance for the seminar?",
            "correct_answer": "19",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "20",
                "Don't know, slept in too many days",
                "Anywehere between 27 and 250"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "TTP",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "medium",
            "question": "What relational database management system did we learn?",
            "correct_answer": "PostgresSQL",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "SQL",
                "mySQL",
                "mongoDB"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "TTP",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "How do you create and enter a new branch using Git?",
            "correct_answer": "git checkout -b branch_name",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "git checkout branch_name",
                "I just push to main everytime",
                "git branch branch_name"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "TTP",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "What does DOM stand for?",
            "correct_answer": "Document Object Model",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Family",
                "Delayed Onset Muscle-Soreness",
                "The Rock"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "TTP",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "Which year does Tenzin wish he was born?",
            "correct_answer": "1994",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "2000",
                "1492",
                "1995"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "TTP",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "Which CSS framework were we briefly introduced to?",
            "correct_answer": "Tailwind",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Bootstrap",
                "Bulma",
                "Foundation"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "TTP",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "hard",
            "question": "What time is lunch everday?",
            "correct_answer": "Depends on Ariel's mood",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "12",
                "1",
                "Y'all still eat??!!"
            ]
        },
        {
            "category": "TTP",
            "type": "multiple",
            "difficulty": "easy",
            "question": "Will you complete the exit survey from Imani Council?",
            "correct_answer": "Of Course I Will!!",
            "incorrect_answers": [
                "Definitely not",
                "Why bother",
                "Don't have time for that"
            ]
        }

    ]
}